{
    "subject": "resource/Scottish_Fuels",
    "predicate": "property/hasPhotoCollection",
    "object": "http://wifo5-03.informatik.uni-mannheim.de/flickrwrappr/photos/Scottish_Fuels",
    "human_readable": "Scottish Fuels has a photo collection.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9736874103546143,
            "question": "Who might have taken the photos in Scottish Fuels' collection?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9676011800765991,
            "question": "Does Scottish Fuels have photos?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9530264139175415,
            "question": "Are the photos in Scottish Fuels' collection publicly accessible?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9499162435531616,
            "question": "What kind of items might be featured in Scottish Fuels' photo collection?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.948752224445343,
            "question": "What is the purpose of Scottish Fuels having a photo collection?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9352986812591553,
            "question": "How are the photos in Scottish Fuels' collection organized?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9324780702590942,
            "question": "What type of equipment might be featured in Scottish Fuels' photo collection?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8988022804260254,
            "question": "Do the photos in Scottish Fuels' collection depict employees or customers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7855137586593628,
            "question": "Could the photos from Scottish Fuels be used for marketing purposes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7789453864097595,
            "question": "Could the photos from Scottish Fuels provide historical insights into the company?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Scottish Fuels has a photo collection.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4425_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Could the photos from Scottish Fuels be used for marketing purposes?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4425_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Do the photos in Scottish Fuels' collection depict employees or customers?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4425_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of equipment might be featured in Scottish Fuels' photo collection?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4425_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4425_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4425_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4425_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4425_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4425_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4425_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4425_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4425_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4425_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4425_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I found that it does not mention anything about Scottish Fuels having a photo collection. However, one of the documents (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_4425/re-ranker-msmarco/102.txt) mentions an image ID (HJK5CF), which suggests that there is at least one photo associated with Scottish Fuels. \n\nBut this does not necessarily mean that Scottish Fuels has a collection of photos.\n\nConsidering the information provided, I would say:\n\n`{'output': 'no'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention several images and photos related to Scottish Fuels, such as image details and thumbnails, which support the statement that Scottish Fuels has a photo collection."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "There is no indication in the provided context information that Scottish Fuels has a photo collection, but rather specific image IDs (HJK5CF and no RMID) which are associated with Alamy Stock Photo. The context suggests that these images are not part of a Scottish Fuels' own photo collection, but rather contributed by a third-party contributor.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}